http://www.miracles.org.uk/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
HOMEEVENTSMIRACLE NETWORK EVENTSMIRACLE CAFEALL EVENTSABOUTABOUT USWHAT IS ACIM?MISSION STATEMENTFAQMIRACLE WORKERGROUPSALPHABETICAL LISTINGINTERACTIVE MAPVIRTUAL GROUPSPROSPECTIVE GROUPSGROUP RESOURCESVIDEO GALLERYMIRACLE FRIENDSSUPPORT USSHOPBOOKSCARDSCDsDVDsDOWNLOADSMIRACLE WORKER MAGAZINEVIEW CARTCONTACT USHOMEEVENTSMIRACLE NETWORK EVENTSMIRACLE CAFEALL EVENTSABOUTABOUT USWHAT IS ACIM?MISSION STATEMENTFAQMIRACLE WORKERGROUPSALPHABETICAL LISTINGINTERACTIVE MAPVIRTUAL STUDY GROUPSPROSPECTIVE GROUPSGROUP RESOURCESVIDEO GALLERYMIRACLE FRIENDSSUPPORT USSHOPBOOKSCARDSCDsDOWNLOADSDVDsMIRACLE WORKER MAGAZINEVIEW CARTCONTACT USHOMEEVENTSMIRACLE NETWORK EVENTSMIRACLE CAFEALL EVENTSABOUTABOUT USWHAT IS ACIM?MISSION STATEMENTFAQMIRACLE WORKERGROUPSALPHABETICAL LISTINGINTERACTIVE MAPVIRTUAL STUDY GROUPSPROSPECTIVE GROUPSGROUP RESOURCESVIDEO GALLERYMIRACLE FRIENDSSUPPORT USSHOPBOOKSCARDSCDsDOWNLOADSDVDsMIRACLE WORKER MAGAZINEVIEW CARTCONTACT US
Privacy PolicyRyan Johnson2019-10-22T11:20:16+01:00
Miracle Network Privacy Policy
Your privacy is always important to the Miracle Network and we have taken the managing of data seriously. To reflect the introduction of the new European General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR), we have updated our Privacy Policy.
This page tells you about the data the Miracle Network collects from you and how we use it, information about your rights and choices with respect to that data, and how to contact us about your privacy or deletion of your data.
Information that we hold about you:
To provide the service and information you have asked for, we need to hold and process personal data.
Some of your personal information we may hold
How we use this information
Your name
To fulfil our promise to inform you.
Your telephone number
To enable us to contact you, if necessary, about any of your dealings with the Miracle Network.
Your email address
To provide you with information about the Miracle Network, events and occasional news about our services.
Your postal address
To enable us to send you Miracle Worker magazine, if you are a subscriber.
Your subscription information (payment date, etc)
To fulfil our obligations to you.
To ensure we are compliant with GDPR:
We use your data only to provide you with the advertised service.
We do not retain credit card information once transactions have been made.
We delete old and obsolete records from our system.
We provide a system for you to opt-out of receiving emails and hard copy mailings from us, if you wish (see below). We assume that you have opted-in by your previous dealings with us, unless you opt-out in the ways described.
Under no circumstances do we share our mailing list, or your data, with any other organisation or individual.
Unsubscribing
Though we don’t want to lose you…
You may unsubscribe from all future emails by clicking on the ‘SafeUnsubscribe’ link at the bottom any email you receive from us.
If you unsubscribe from our email list in error, or want to resubscribe at any time in the future, you can get back on the list using the ‘Join Our Mailing List’ on the Homepage or Contact pages.
You may unsubscribe from Miracle Worker magazine by sending us an email – click here.
Go to Top
